Privacy Policy
--------------

This privacy policy governs your use of the software application ("Application") for mobile devices that was created by KiteTech.  

#### What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?

**Automatically Collected Information** 

The Application may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile devices unique device ID, your mobile operating system, and information about the way you use the Application. 

#### Does the Application collect precise real time location information of the device?

This Application does not collect precise information about the location of your mobile device. 

#### Do third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?

No. Third parties cannot see or have access to information obtained by the Application.

#### Automatic Data Collection and Advertising

We may work with analytics companies to help us understand how the Application is being used, such as the frequency and duration of usage. We work with advertisers and third party advertising networks, who need to know how you interact with advertising provided in the Application which helps us keep the cost of the Application low. Advertisers and advertising networks use some of the information collected by the Application, including, but not limited to, the unique identification ID of your mobile device. These third parties may also obtain anonymous information about other applications you've downloaded to your mobile device in order to help analyze and serve anonymous targeted advertising on the Application and elsewhere.  

If you'd like to opt-out from third party use of this type of information to help serve targeted advertising, please visit the section entitled "Opt-out" below. 

#### What are my opt-out rights?

You can opt-out of all information collection by uninstalling the Application: You can stop all collection of information by the Application easily by uninstalling the Application. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network.

#### **Children**

We do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at support@kitetech.co. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.

#### **Security**

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Application. Please be aware that, although we endeavor provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.

#### **Changes**

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes.

#### **Your Consent**

By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing," means using touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information. 

#### Contact us

If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at support@kitetech.co.
